{
    "subject": "resource/Carmit_Bachar",
    "predicate": "ontology/hometown",
    "object": "resource/United_States",
    "human_readable": "Carmit Bachar is from United States.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9810035228729248,
            "question": "Is Carmit Bachar a citizen of the United States?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9454537034034729,
            "question": "Is Carmit Bachar of American descent?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9425228834152222,
            "question": "Is Carmit Bachar American?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8305665254592896,
            "question": "Where is Carmit Bachar from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7806829214096069,
            "question": "What is Carmit Bachar's origin?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7165192365646362,
            "question": "Where was Carmit Bachar born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6577612161636353,
            "question": "What is the nationality of Carmit Bachar?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.656650960445404,
            "question": "What country is Carmit Bachar associated with?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6522033214569092,
            "question": "To which country does Carmit Bachar belong?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5181047320365906,
            "question": "Can you tell me Carmit Bachar's nationality?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Carmit Bachar is from United States.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8948_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=To which country does Carmit Bachar belong?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8948_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What country is Carmit Bachar associated with?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8948_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the nationality of Carmit Bachar?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8948_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8948_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8948_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8948_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8948_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8948_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8948_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8948_72.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8948_86.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8948_91.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8948_99.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\nLet me know if you have more triples to evaluate!  I'm ready. \ud83d\ude0a \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Based on the context information provided, I can evaluate the triple \"Carmit Bachar is from United States.\"\n\nThe answer is:\n\n`{'output': 'yes'}`"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents mention that Carmit Bachar was born in Los Angeles, California, United States, and describes her as an American singer, dancer, model, actress, and showgirl. This supports the statement that Carmit Bachar is from the United States."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 0,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Most Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "mistral": {
            "reason": "Carmit Bachar is an American by nationality, as she was born in the United States.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "Several sources state she was born in Los Angeles, California.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "The claim is wrong because Carmit Bachar's father is Israeli Jewish and her mother has Dutch, small amounts of Indonesian, and Chinese ethnicity.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "reason": "Carmit Bachar has both American and Israeli origins. She was born in Los Angeles, California, United States, but she is also described as an \"American-Israeli\" singer, indicating her connection to Israel as well. Therefore, stating she is solely from the United States is inaccurate.",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}